<?xml version="1.0"?>
<info xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
	  xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://apps.nextcloud.com/schema/apps/info.xsd">
	<id>nldesign</id>
	<name lang="en">NL Design System Theme</name>
	<name lang="nl">NL Design System Thema</name>
	<summary lang="en">Brand your Nextcloud with 39 Dutch government design token sets</summary>
	<summary lang="nl">Geef je Nextcloud de huisstijl van je organisatie met 39 design token sets</summary>
	<description lang="en"><![CDATA[NL Design System Theme transforms your Nextcloud into a fully branded government workspace. Pick your organization's token set, and the entire interface updates to match your official design standards — colors, typography, and all.

**Key Features**

- **39 token sets** — Rijkshuisstijl (national government), Amsterdam, Utrecht, Rotterdam, Den Haag, and 34 more municipalities and organizations
- **One-click theming** — Select your token set in admin settings and the entire Nextcloud interface adapts instantly
- **Live preview** — See your chosen colors and typography before activating
- **WCAG AA accessible** — All token sets are designed for accessibility compliance
- **No build required** — Pure CSS-based theming, lightweight and fast
- **Fira Sans included** — Open-source font bundled for consistent government typography
- **Smart fallbacks** — Incomplete token sets automatically inherit from Rijkshuisstijl defaults
- **Extra options** — Hide the login page slogan, show text labels in the app menu, sync Nextcloud logos with your token set

Works seamlessly with all Nextcloud apps that follow standard theming conventions.

Free and open source under the AGPL license.
	]]></description>
	<description lang="nl"><![CDATA[NL Design System Thema maakt van je Nextcloud een volledig huisstijl-conforme overheidswerkplek. Kies de token set van je organisatie en de hele interface past zich direct aan — kleuren, typografie en meer.

**Belangrijkste functies**

- **39 token sets** — Rijkshuisstijl (rijksoverheid), Amsterdam, Utrecht, Rotterdam, Den Haag en 34 andere gemeenten en organisaties
- **Theming met een klik** — Selecteer je token set in de beheerinstellingen en de hele Nextcloud-interface past zich direct aan
- **Live preview** — Bekijk je gekozen kleuren en typografie voordat je activeert
- **WCAG AA toegankelijk** — Alle token sets zijn ontworpen voor toegankelijkheidscompliance
- **Geen build nodig** — Puur CSS-gebaseerde theming, lichtgewicht en snel
- **Fira Sans inbegrepen** — Open-source lettertype meegeleverd voor consistente overheidstypografie
- **Slimme fallbacks** — Onvolledige token sets erven automatisch van Rijkshuisstijl-standaardwaarden
- **Extra opties** — Verberg de slogan op de loginpagina, toon tekstlabels in het app-menu, synchroniseer Nextcloud-logo's met je token set

Werkt naadloos samen met alle Nextcloud-apps die standaard theming-conventies volgen.

Vrij en open source onder de AGPL-licentie.
	]]></description>
	<version>0.1.1-unstable.14</version>
	<licence>agpl</licence>
	<author mail="info@conduction.nl" homepage="https://www.conduction.nl/">Conduction</author>
	<namespace>NLDesign</namespace>
	<documentation>
		<user>https://github.com/ConductionNL/nldesign</user>
		<admin>https://github.com/ConductionNL/nldesign</admin>
		<developer>https://github.com/ConductionNL/nldesign</developer>
	</documentation>
	<category>customization</category>
	<website>https://github.com/ConductionNL/nldesign</website>
	<discussion>https://github.com/ConductionNL/nldesign/discussions</discussion>
	<bugs>https://github.com/ConductionNL/nldesign/issues</bugs>
	<repository type="git">https://github.com/ConductionNL/nldesign.git</repository>

	<screenshot>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ConductionNL/nldesign/main/img/app-store.svg</screenshot>
	<screenshot>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ConductionNL/nldesign/main/img/screenshot.png</screenshot>

	<dependencies>
		<php min-version="8.1"/>
		<nextcloud min-version="28" max-version="33"/>
	</dependencies>
	<settings>
		<admin>OCA\NLDesign\Settings\Admin</admin>
		<admin-section>theming</admin-section>
	</settings>
</info>
